indicustom.com 2011-10-17

# indi - Privacy Statement

SUMMARY 

At indi we take your privacy very seriously. Please read this Privacy Policy to learn more about how we treat personally identifiable and other information. We provide this Privacy Policy because you have a right to know what information we collect, how it is protected and used, and the circumstances under which it may be disclosed. If you have comments, suggestions, questions, or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us via email at , or in writing at: Attention: Management, indi, 5515 Doyle Street, Suite #15, Emeryville, CA 94608. 

Online Privacy Standards. While there are no official standards governing privacy practices on the internet, we follow the principles supported by the Federal Trade Commission’s Fair Information Practices Principles, currently available at   
<http://www.ftc.gov/reports/privacy3/fairinfo.htm>. 

What This Privacy Policy Covers. This Privacy Policy covers indi’s treatment of personally identifiable that we obtain when you visit [www.indiCustom.com](http://www.indicustom.com/) (the "Site"), elect to receive promotional materials, or register an account. We regard personally identifiable information as information that can be used to identify or contact you in person, such as real name, telephone number, email address, physical mailing address, and body measurements. 

What This Privacy Policy Does Not Cover. From time to time, our Site will link to websites that are controlled by third parties. This statement does not cover the privacy practices of third parties that we do not own or control, such as our partners and advertisers, nor does it cover the privacy practices of third parties through which Content and Comments (defined below) can be shared, such as Digg, Facebook, and the like. All of these external sites operate independently of indi and they each have their own privacy or security practices. For your best online experience, we encourage you to review their policies before submitting any personal information to them. If you do provide information to a retailer or other business featured by indi, any transaction that may result will occur through that company’s website and not our own website. indi acts solely as the facilitator of that transaction and does not control, and is not responsible for, the privacy practices of those other businesses. We encourage you to seek information about safeguarding your online privacy from experts such as the Federal Trade Commission. 

HOW INFORMATION IS COLLECTED 

1\. Information You Provide.

Required Registration Information. During the process of registering an account (your “account profile”), we will collect your first and last name, email address, and ask you to select a password. Your email address will also serve to identify your account profile in our system and you will use your email address to login to your account. 

Body Measurements. During the process of creating your custom order, we also collect information reflecting your body measurements, body shape and sizes typically purchased. This information is necessary so that we can customize the fit of your garment. This information is stored in our database and cannot be edited from within your account profile. To make adjustments to a garment you have previously ordered, please use our re-order tool. Read our re-order FAQ to learn more. 

Information Submitted During A Transaction. . During a payment transaction we collect information including your name, shipping and billing address(es), email address, and telephone number. This information is collected and used to process your payment transaction, and also for shipping your apparel to you. The shipping address you provide during a payment transaction will be stored in your account profile. 

indi does not itself collect any financial information from you. Instead, your transactions are handled through Authorize.Net. The Site allows you to use Authorize.Net to conveniently make payments online using a credit card. Before using Authorize.Net, indi strongly suggests that you review Authorize.Net's own privacy policy, which is available online at the Authorize.Net website [www.authorize.net](http://www.authorize.net/). 

Comments. When commenting on custom designs created by users of the Site ("Comments"), the free-form textbox in which Comments may be made can be used to enter any text – including personally identifiable information. Such information will be visible to all users of the Site who view Comments for that garment. For this reason, you should only include information in your Comments that you wish to share with the public. 

2\. Information We Do Not Collect.

Children. As explained further in our Terms of Use, available at [www.inditailored.com/terms](http://www.inditailored.com/terms), you must be eighteen (18) years of age or older to use the Site. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from or about children. If you believe that we have information from or about anyone under 13 years of age, please notify us by email at  or write to us at the address noted above in the first paragraph of this Privacy Policy. 

Social Security Number. We do not ask for or require you to provide your social security number to use any of our services or to access any part of our Site. 

Birth Date. We do not ask for or require you to reveal your birth date to use any of our services or to access any part of our Site. 

3\. Information We Track.

Log Files. Similar to many websites, we gather certain anonymous, non-personal information automatically and store it in web server log files when you visit our Site, including when you create an account profile, sign-in, search, fill out a survey, or request our e-mail newsletter. This information includes internet protocol addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), site entry/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information to improve the Site, analyze trends, administer the Site, track users’ movements around the Site, address security issues, and gather aggregate information about our user base as a whole. Aggregate information is data we collect about a group or category of services or account profile holders from which individual member identities have been removed, and therefore does not include your personally identifiable information. 

Cookies. A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. It can also help us understand how our site visitors click to our site, and what pages they view during their visit. Similar to many websites, we store an encrypted cookie on your computer so we can remember you when you come back to our website without requiring you to log-in every time. Cookies also allow us to track and understand the interests of our users to enhance the overall experience on our site. 

You can set your web browser software to disable cookies. To do so, please refer to the help section of your specific browser for more information on how to manage or disable cookies. If you disable cookies, you may still view our site, but some areas of our site may not work properly. 

HOW INFORMATION IS USED 

1\. In Communications from indi.

We use emails and/or prominent notifications on our website as our primary means to inform our members of important service and promotional announcements. 

Required Communications. We use your email address to deliver important system-related and other required communications. Examples of these required communications include: an email sent to confirm the creation of your account profile; requests for password reset, order confirmation, shipping notification, important security or server maintenance updates, changes to our policies (like our terms of use or this Privacy Policy), and post-purchase consumer satisfaction surveys. These communications are considered a fundamental part of our Site and our service, and account profile holders cannot opt-out of these announcements. 

Promotional Material. In order to improve the experience for our account profile holders, we will offer you the ability to sign up for optional email material, such as promotional offers and periodic newsletters. These materials are enhancements to our service and are entirely optional. We will ask for your consent before sending you promotional material, and will make it easy for you to unsubscribe, or opt-out, either through email or though your account profile. 

2\. For Our Site Statistics. As noted above, we may use information collected from our web log files to calculate and publish anonymous, non-personal, aggregate statistics that we believe those who use and visit the Site are interested in viewing. For example, we may track and publish the total number of people who have viewed a particular page. We publish this data in aggregate form only, and do not tie it to any personally identifiable information. 

3\. For Internal Reporting And Analysis. As noted above, we use information gathered from log files and cookies to improve the Site, analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movements around the Site, and to gather aggregate information about those who browse and use the Site as a whole. We do not tie this data to personally identifiable information. We may also use body measurement data to improve our service. When used for this purpose, body measurement data is not tied to personally identifiable information. 

4\. Design Statistics. If you use the Site to create and share a custom clothing design(s), we may link that design to your personally identifiable information for the purposes of tracking the popularity of your design among users of the Site. This information may be published on the Site and/or used for internal analysis. 

HOW INFORMATION IS SHARED AND DISCLOSED 

1\. With Third-Parties.

Sharing, Renting, And Selling Information We Collect. We will neither rent nor sell your personally identifiable information to anyone. We may share anonymous, non-personal, aggregate information about our user base with partners or advertisers, and we may publish these aggregate usage statistics on our website as described above. We do not tie this shared or published data to personally identifiable information. 

We may share your personally identifiable information with third parties and affiliates with whom we have contracted to perform services on our behalf (for example, shipping companies and companies who assist in the manufacture of our apparel). All such companies are obligated to maintain the information we provide to them in confidence and to use that information only to provide the services we ask them to perform. No third parties with whom we may share your personally identifiable information are authorized to use the information for any direct marketing activities unrelated to our Site. 

2\. As Necessary In Certain Legal Circumstances.

Legal Requirements. We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website. 

Acquisition Or Other Transfer. If our company is acquired, all of our assets, including your personally identifiable information, may be transferred to the acquiring company. At that time, your account information, including personally identifiable information, may become subject to the acquiring company’s privacy policy. In addition, in the event that we must liquidate our assets due to bankruptcy or other event, we will consider our customer information, including personally identifiable information, as a unique asset subject to sale or other transfer. Before we transfer your information under such a scenario, we will notify you either by email or by posting a notice on our site, and we will remind you of your ability to edit or disable your personally identifiable information from your account profile in advance of any such transfer. 

HOW INFORMATION IS KEPT SECURE 

Security of Account Information. Your account profile information is password-protected. We will not share your password with anyone. Please do not share your password with anyone, and remember to change your password from time to time, to keep your account profile information secure. 

Network Security. We have implemented a variety of commercially standard encryption and security technologies and procedures to protect information, including your personal information, stored in our computer systems from unauthorized access. Please be aware that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, thus we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, but we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

Management Procedures. We also maintain standard physical and electronic procedural safeguards that limit access to your personally identifiable information to our employees (or people working on our behalf and under confidentiality agreements) who, through the course of standard business activities, need to access your personally identifiable information. 

YOUR PERSONAL CHOICES 

Receiving Communications. If you opt to receive any of indi’s optional promotional materials, you will be able to unsubscribe from these materials through your account profile or through the emails we send you. If you elect not to receive such promotional material by email, we may still contact you as necessary to service your account. 

Access To And Editing Account Profile Information. In general, we make it easy for you to view the personally identifiable information we have collected from you in your account profile, where you can edit your information as you see fit. If you would like to permanently disable your account, please email . 

FOR OUR CANADIAN MEMBERS AND VISITORS 

Canadian citizens, except under circumstances defined by law, are entitled to access their own personally identifiable information collected by indi by writing to: Attention: Management, indi, 5515 Doyle St., Suite #15, Emeryville, CA 94608. We may ask you to pay an administrative fee for accessing or copying your information, but will inform you of the anticipated charges and confirm that you want us to proceed before processing your request. If you believe that the personally identifiable information about you that we have collected is incomplete or inaccurate, we will correct the information upon verification of the omission or error and of the identity of the person requesting the change. If you would like to receive additional information about our personal information management practices, to access, correct or have us investigate any matters in relation to your personally identifiable information, please contact us at the address provided above. 

UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY 

Our Site and service is evolving and developing. From time to time, we will review and make changes to this Privacy Policy. When we do so, we will notify you either by email or place a prominent notice on our Site. The most recent version of our Privacy Policy is always available from a link on our homepage or at [www.indiCustom.com/privacy](http://www.indicustom.com/privacy). We encourage you to visit this site frequently to stay up to date on our current policy.
